(Leonard:)What you doing?
(Sheldon:)I'm setting out snacks.
(Leonard:)You do realize everyone's eating
at Raj's again tonight.
(Sheldon:)I didn't say the snacks were
for you now, did I, Nosy Rosie?
(Leonard:)You're having people over?
(Sheldon:)Yes. Must be killing you
wondering who.
(Sheldon:)Fine, I'll tell you.
(Sheldon:)Stuart from the
comic bookstore,
(Sheldon:)Barry Kripke from
the university,
(Sheldon:)Penny's ex-boyfriend Zack
(Sheldon:)and TV's LeVar Burton.
(Leonard:)Really?
(Leonard:)LeVar Burton's coming here?
(Sheldon:)Possibly. I Tweeted him.
Okay, well, tell him
I loved him on Star Trek.
(Sheldon:)Please, Leonard, stop trying
to horn in on my new friends.
(Leonard:)Of course. Good night.
(Sheldon:)Leonard.
Yeah?
(Sheldon:)We had a good run, you and I.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)But change is a part of life.